<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <option name="newTranslationDialogCollapseDictViewer" value="false" />
    <option name="newTranslationDialogWidth" value="554" />
    <option name="newTranslationDialogX" value="826" />
    <option name="newTranslationDialogY" value="470" />
    <option name="pinNewTranslationDialog" value="true" />
    <histories>
      <item value="`ABSOLUTE`, position graphic using only its Z value. `RELATIVE`, position graphic using its Z value plus the altitude values of the scene. `DRAPED_BILLBOARDED`, position graphic upright on the surface and always facing the camera, not using its z value. `DRAPED_FLAT`, position graphic flat on the surface, not using its z value. `RELATIVE_TO_SCENE`, position graphic using the Z value of the scene layer.`" />
      <item value="scene" />
      <item value="surface" />
      <item value="TRIANGLE" />
      <item value="ABSOLUTE" />
      <item value="RELATIVE" />
      <item value="BILLBOARDED" />
      <item value="DRAPED BILLBOARDED" />
      <item value="DRAPED" />
      <item value="draped Flat Overlay" />
      <item value="draped Billboarded Overlay" />
      <item value="Auto Pan Mode" />
      <item value="Mode" />
      <item value="DYNAMIC" />
      <item value="vertical Accuracy" />
      <item value="horizontal Accuracy" />
      <item value="velocity" />
      <item value="Simple Renderer" />
      <item value="renderer" />
      <item value="operational Layers" />
      <item value="Raster Elevation Source" />
      <item value="elevation Sources" />
      <item value="elevation" />
      <item value="raster&#10;" />
      <item value="ras" />
      <item value="terrain" />
      <item value="terr" />
      <item value="Initiate peer discovery. A discovery process involves scanning for available Wi-Fi peers for the purpose of establishing a connection. &lt;p&gt; The function call immediately returns after sending a discovery request to the framework. The application is notified of a success or failure to initiate discovery through listener callbacks {@link ActionListeneronSuccess} or {@link ActionListeneronFailure}. &lt;p&gt; The discovery remains active until a connection is initiated or a p2p group is formed. Register for {@link WIFI_P2P_PEERS_CHANGED_ACTION} intent to determine when the framework notifies of a change as peers are discovered. &lt;p&gt; Upon receiving a {@link WIFI_P2P_PEERS_CHANGED_ACTION} intent, an application can request for the list of peers using {@link requestPeers}. @param c is the channel created at {@link initialize} @param listener for callbacks on success or failure. Can be null." />
      <item value="exists" />
      <item value="destination" />
      <item value="剩下的" />
      <item value="yu" />
      <item value="余数" />
      <item value="yushu" />
      <item value="Reads up to &lt;code&gt;len&lt;code&gt; bytes of data from the input stream into an array of bytes. An attempt is made to read as many as &lt;code&gt;len&lt;code&gt; bytes, but a smaller number may be read. The number of bytes actually read is returned as an integer. &lt;p&gt; This method blocks until input data is available, end of file is detected, or an exception is thrown. &lt;p&gt; If &lt;code&gt;len&lt;code&gt; is zero, then no bytes are read and &lt;code&gt;0&lt;code&gt; is returned; otherwise, there is an attempt to read at least one byte. If no byte is available because the stream is at end of file, the value &lt;code&gt;-1&lt;code&gt; is returned; otherwise, at least one byte is read and stored into &lt;code&gt;b&lt;code&gt;. &lt;p&gt; The first byte read is stored into element &lt;code&gt;b[off]&lt;code&gt;, the next one into &lt;code&gt;b[off+1]&lt;code&gt;, and so on. The number of bytes read is, at most, equal to &lt;code&gt;len&lt;code&gt;. Let &lt;i&gt;k&lt;i&gt; be the number of bytes actually read; these bytes will be stored in elements &lt;code&gt;b[off]&lt;code&gt; through &lt;code&gt;b[off+&lt;code&gt;&lt;i&gt;k&lt;i&gt;&lt;code&gt;-1]&lt;code&gt;, leaving elements &lt;code&gt;b[off+&lt;code&gt;&lt;i&gt;k&lt;i&gt;&lt;code&gt;]&lt;code&gt; through &lt;code&gt;b[off+len-1]&lt;code&gt; unaffected. &lt;p&gt; In every case, elements &lt;code&gt;b[0]&lt;code&gt; through &lt;code&gt;b[off]&lt;code&gt; and elements &lt;code&gt;b[off+len]&lt;code&gt; through &lt;code&gt;b[b.length-1]&lt;code&gt; are unaffected. &lt;p&gt; The &lt;code&gt;read(b,&lt;code&gt; &lt;code&gt;off,&lt;code&gt; &lt;code&gt;len)&lt;code&gt; method for class &lt;code&gt;InputStream&lt;code&gt; simply calls the method &lt;code&gt;read()&lt;code&gt; repeatedly. If the first such call results in an &lt;code&gt;IOException&lt;code&gt;, that exception is returned from the call to the &lt;code&gt;read(b,&lt;code&gt; &lt;code&gt;off,&lt;code&gt; &lt;code&gt;len)&lt;code&gt; method. If any subsequent call to &lt;code&gt;read()&lt;code&gt; results in a &lt;code&gt;IOException&lt;code&gt;, the exception is caught and treated as if it were end of file; the bytes read up to that point are stored into &lt;code&gt;b&lt;code&gt; and the number of bytes read before the exception occurred is returned. The default implementation of this method blocks until the requested amount of input data &lt;code&gt;len&lt;code&gt; has been read, end of file is detected, or an exception is thrown. Subclasses are encouraged to provide a more efficient implementation of this method. @param b the buffer into which the data is read. @param off the start offset in array &lt;code&gt;b&lt;code&gt; at which the data is written. @param len the maximum number of bytes to read. @return the total number of bytes read into the buffer, or &lt;code&gt;-1&lt;code&gt; if there is no more data because the end of the stream has been reached. @exception IOException If the first byte cannot be read for any reason other than end of file, or if the input stream has been closed, or if some other IO error occurs. @exception NullPointerException If &lt;code&gt;b&lt;code&gt; is &lt;code&gt;null&lt;code&gt;. @exception IndexOutOfBoundsException If &lt;code&gt;off&lt;code&gt; is negative, &lt;code&gt;len&lt;code&gt; is negative, or &lt;code&gt;len&lt;code&gt; is greater than &lt;code&gt;b.length - off&lt;code&gt; @see java.io.InputStreamread()" />
      <item value="Returns an estimate of the number of bytes that can be read (or skipped over) from this input stream without blocking by the next invocation of a method for this input stream. The next invocation might be the same thread or another thread. A single read or skip of this many bytes will not block, but may read or skip fewer bytes. &lt;p&gt; Note that while some implementations of {@code InputStream} will return the total number of bytes in the stream, many will not. It is never correct to use the return value of this method to allocate a buffer intended to hold all data in this stream. &lt;p&gt; A subclass' implementation of this method may choose to throw an {@link IOException} if this input stream has been closed by invoking the {@link close()} method. &lt;p&gt; The {@code available} method for class {@code InputStream} always returns {@code 0}. &lt;p&gt; This method should be overridden by subclasses. @return an estimate of the number of bytes that can be read (or skipped over) from this input stream without blocking or {@code 0} when it reaches the end of the input stream. @exception IOException if an IO error occurs." />
      <item value="The channel to the framework has been disconnected. Application could try re-initializing using {@link initialize}" />
      <item value="Indicates if a p2p group has been successfully formed" />
      <item value="group Formed" />
      <item value="Justify " />
      <item value="treat As Downloadable" />
      <item value="As" />
      <item value="TLS CERT POLICY INSECURE NO CHECK" />
      <item value="TLS" />
      <item value="UNINITIALIZED" />
      <item value="HEADSET UNAVAILABLE" />
      <item value="Abandoned" />
      <item value="Reads the next byte of data from the input stream. The value byte is returned as an &lt;code&gt;int&lt;code&gt; in the range &lt;code&gt;0&lt;code&gt; to &lt;code&gt;255&lt;code&gt;. If no byte is available because the end of the stream has been reached, the value &lt;code&gt;-1&lt;code&gt; is returned. This method blocks until input data is available, the end of the stream is detected, or an exception is thrown. &lt;p&gt; A subclass must provide an implementation of this method. @return the next byte of data, or &lt;code&gt;-1&lt;code&gt; if the end of the stream is reached. @exception IOException if an IO error occurs." />
      <item value="Returns an estimate of the number of remaining bytes that can be read (or skipped over) from this input stream without blocking by the next invocation of a method for this input stream. Returns 0 when the file position is beyond EOF. The next invocation might be the same thread or another thread. A single read or skip of this many bytes will not block, but may read or skip fewer bytes. &lt;p&gt; In some cases, a non-blocking read (or skip) may appear to be blocked when it is merely slow, for example when reading large files over slow networks. @return an estimate of the number of remaining bytes that can be read (or skipped over) from this input stream without blocking. @exception IOException if this file input stream has been closed by calling {@code close} or an IO error occurs." />
      <item value="File unsuitable for memory mapping" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="773" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="774" />
        <entry key="POLISH" value="2" />
        <entry key="GERMAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="FRENCH" value="12" />
        <entry key="CATALAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="KANNADA" value="1" />
        <entry key="LATIN" value="2" />
        <entry key="ROMANIAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="JAPANESE" value="4" />
        <entry key="SWEDISH" value="2" />
        <entry key="WELSH" value="2" />
        <entry key="SPANISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="GREEK" value="3" />
        <entry key="HUNGARIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="ITALIAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="HINDI" value="3" />
        <entry key="INDONESIAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="VIETNAMESE" value="1" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Cache">
    <option name="lastTrimTime" value="1618190874850" />
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="overrideFont" value="true" />
    <option name="phoneticFontFamily" value="Arial" />
    <option name="primaryFontFamily" value="SimSun" />
    <option name="translateDocumentation" value="true" />
  </component>
</application>